Fate, wake up!
Then again, I guess that's off the table,
considering he was drugged.
Dammit! What the hell do we do now?
It's ready.
The Girl of Wrath
Where's Fate?! Bring out the sacrifice—
Someone help—
Now spit it up.
Here's some water.
Okay...
An antidote, huh?
This village really does know its herbs.
Where...?
We're in my house.
You were drugged and put to sleep.
Drugged?
It was my father's doing. I'm sorry.
Stay inside the house, Set.
What a nightmare...
Fate!
We're in trouble if they
keep taking shots at us from above.
Yeah.
They're level 27,
with Fireball as their skill.
[Stats]
Vitality:
Strength:
Magic:
Spirit:
Agility:
[Skills]
Fireball
That skill could spell trouble.
Use the great scythe!
Got it!
Let's go!
I thought it was supposed to
cut through the ephemeral!
Well, it cut the magic, but the fire
that it causes is a whole separate issue.
I think I get it.
I think they do, too.
They're going for blanket fire now
instead of just hitting you.
Let's see...
How they like this!
Gluttony skill has activated.
The skill Fireball has been added.
That leaves...
Just the leader, now.
Level 47... His skills are Fireball
and Fire Resistance.
[Stats]
Vitality:
Strength:
Magic:
Spirit:
Agility:
[Skills]
Fireball
Fire Resistance
Fate, he's gonna close in
to hit you with that Fireball.
That'll be your chance!
Got it!
Gluttony skill has activated.
Increasing stats.
The skill Fire Resistance
has been added.
My dad's dead.
Only a few villagers survived, including me.
The village is finished.
Let me take a look.
This land is done for.
The soil isn't healthy.
You won't be able to grow anything here.
Fate... you can use Identify?
Yeah.
Then why do something dangerous
like being a warrior?
You could earn your living with Identify.
Gluttony... a skill that defies divine law.
I have no choice but to fight.
I'm gonna look for a job in town...
For my daughter's sake.
Look, Fate. I want you to hit me.
I want to pay for what I did. Please.
Let him have it, Fate.
It'll help him feel even.
Fine...
Set, grit your teeth.
R-Right!
Aw, come on, that was too hard!
You total oaf!
H-Huh?
Thanks, Fate.
Y-You okay?
Yeah.
Look after your daughter, Set.
I will. Take care, Fate.
As bad as this village was,
I hate to see it go.
But... the memories of my time
here with Dad aren't gone.
I'm gonna be fine from now on, Dad.
We're nearly to Lanchester
territory, Lady Roxy.
Yes. Once we get there,
we'll see about resupplying.
Be careful around the lord
of Lanchester, Lady Roxy.
What do you mean, Mugan?
You'll see when we get there.
He's holding out on us!
That's cheap, Mugan! Cheap, cheap, cheap!
Cheapskate old man!
Would you stop saying cheap?!
You're not a bird!
Hey, come on, mister...
I see you yawning back there.
Are you guarding me or what?
Sorry about that.
I'm paying you three gold coins, here.
I'm counting on you if things get rough.
Guy thinks he's hot stuff
for three gold coins...
You don't need to worry.
I may not look it, but I can fight decently.
About as well as a rookie holy knight.
Bold claim!
That's a relief to hear!
You in the carriage!
Sorry, but the road's closed.
If you don't wanna die,
leave everything of value behind!
Here they are!
Hold it! You'll have to deal with me.
See? You should've asked for more pay.
You always live up to your name, Greed.
S-S-Save me!
What the—?!
You're strong, aren't you, mister?!
You gotta do something!
Just get off of me! I can't fight like this!
I got a wife, a six-year-old,
and a seven-year-old at home!
Save me! Don't run off!
Look there, boys, the prey's
shaking in his boots!
Let's take 'em down!
I only know one person
who could pull that off...
Found you.
It's you... from before.
You owe me for those kobolds.
I could use a ride.
Sure. Considering you
helped us... Hop in.
The carriage tipped over?!
Sloth, go back to normal.
The weight of her weapon changed?
Didn't get your name yet.
It's Fate Graphite.
Fate of Gluttony. Got it.
How do you know about that?!
I have a Skill of Deadly Sin, too.
Of course I can tell.
Skill of Deadly Sin...?
Did Greed not tell you about them?
Greed...!
I'm Myne of Wrath. Nice to meet you.
Wrath...?
Hungry...
Want some jerky?
Huh? Whoa—
Don't eat all of it!
My share...
We're almost in town.
Someone, help!
Rest easy, miss.
I will deal with them.
We're done for!
How gallant! What's your name?
I am none other than the lord
of Lanchester, Rudolph.
Sir Rudolph! You're so wonderful!
What kind of sideshow is that?
Looks like Sir Rudolph is preparing
to welcome the expedition to Galia.
Do you mean the one led by Lady Roxy?
Yeah! They should be coming to town soon.
Wait, you mean—?
You were running after her
and ended up passing her by!
Considering the numbers
and supplies they're packing,
it makes sense they'd be slower.
Here you are, the three
gold coins I promised.
Oh, right.
I'll take those.
I saved him.
Greedy jerk!
Well, that's ironic.
Thanks for the help, folks.
Sure.
Now, then... what next?
Guess we should find somewhere to stay.
Right.
Whoa—Don't fall asleep on your feet...
How did I end up doing this?
Give it up. She's not exactly
a morning person.
You seem pretty well acquainted.
The quiet act again?
Shhh! Or people are gonna think you're
some weirdo who talks to himself.
Welcome to Lanchester.
Our great lord, Sir Rudolph, welcomes you.
Do they revere the holy knights
in this town...?
What are those symbols?
Travelers can't pass any further.
Only citizens can enter past here.
You'll find lodging over there.
They've got a different mark
on their neck than the others.
Welcome to Lanchester.
Another different mark...
What is going on here?
Most likely different social classes.
Looks like the lord here doesn't even pretend
that they're not on a caste system.
The people must truly love him.
Is that what it is...?
That was your idea of a ceremony?!
That was no way to convey how great
I... no, the Lanchester family is!
The whole point of this is to
demonstrate our superiority to the Harts!
Are you trying to humiliate me?!
Please, forgive us, Sir Rudo—
You're that warrior who ran off
during a monster hunt.
Worthless fools.
Two in one day... He's getting worse.
If we upset Sir Rudolph,
we'll end up dead, too.
She really is a handful.
I didn't expect her to still be alive...
You didn't?
How do you know Myne anyway, Greed?
We're old acquaintances who keep
running into each other.
That also goes for Sloth, over there.
Myne's axe?
Yeah. Sloth is like me—
a Weapon of Mortal Sin.
Myne mentioned something
about Skills of Deadly Sin, too.
What is all this stuff?
I guess it's time that you
actually learn about them, Fate.
Gluttony.
Wrath.
Greed.
Sloth.
Lust.
Envy.
And Pride.
These skills were born by defying
the laws put forth by the divine...
Which is why they are called the Skills
of Deadly Sin and Weapons of Mortal Sin.
Among them, Gluttony
is particularly sinful
for having the potential to
overturn the divine system of leveling.
Sin... so that's it.
Once Gluttony tasted souls,
there was no stopping it.
And that's my punishment.
We all have to pay,
in one way or another.
Same goes for Myne.
Why me, though?
I get mocked, made a fool of,
for a useless skill that just
makes me hungry all the time...
And just when I think
I had gained some power,
I have to keep killing to survive.
What good even is this power?!
Whoa, now, that kind of emotional
disturbance could cost you, someday.
Maybe even today.
If your mind isn't resilient,
Gluttony will take it over.
You need to get strong
enough to resist, Fate.
The strength to resist...
The trick is to sustain
a state of near-starvation.
Let's go.
Listen up. Don't satisfy
Gluttony all at once...
You'll wanna slowly get your fill.
Got it.
A Sandman, huh?
Okay, let's try this out on him.
Cast Fireball before you fire the arrow.
Okay.
Wow...
I can add the Fireball skill
to the magic arrow?
Who do you think I am?
Gluttony skill has activated.
Hang in there, Fate.
Another sandman, huh?
You have to suck it up, Fate.
Whoa, even more sandmen...
Hang on!
This is gonna be a long night...
Hungry.
"Whoever defeats the sand
golem will be rewarded."
Even Sir Rudolph can't slay the sand golem.
But if it isn't defeated,
then only death awaits...
Gluttony skill has activated.
Looks like you're getting the hang of it.
Feels a bit like only drinking a drop
of water at a time in the desert.
I guess it's time to satisfy Gluttony, then.
Don't want you going nuts, after all.
This scent... there's
a Crowned Beast nearby.
That'll make a fine main dish for you.
Are you okay?!
Leave us and run!
We can't do that!
But how do we stop this thing?
What the...?
This monster is mine.
Hey! You can't beat this thing on your own!
Playing hero again?
No.
I'm just getting my fill.
Eye of the Sandstorm
[Stats]
Vitality:
Strength:
Magic:
Spirit:
Agility:
[Skills]
Sandstorm
That's Sandstorm!
Once he pulls you in,
he'll crush you with rocks!
Fine, then. I'll cut
through him and his spell!
Great scythe, Greed!
Changing!
Begone!
Now we'll cut him apart!
End it, Fate!
Right!
The core's gone inside the sand!
Don't let it get away!
Bloody Ptarmigan, Greed!
Take your 10%!
Not enough! I'll need 20% for this!
Fine! And take some fire while you're at it!
Oh, gladly!
Gluttony skill has activated.
The skill Sandstorm has been added.
What a mess...
There was no other way to win.
It is what it is.
That was really something!
I've never seen a warrior that
could do something like that before.
Pretty shady looking, though!
You really did save us, though. Thanks.
It's fine. Just lending a helping hand.
I'm Bard. What's your name?
I'm Corpse.
Is that all of your gear, Corpse?
Yeah. You think I should get some more?
You won't need it.
You can steal enemy skills
and increase your stats.
Most people can't, so they need equipment.
The power to defy
the concept of levels, huh?
Why aren't you wearing anything,
Myne?! Get dressed!
You're just a kid, Fate.
Why would I be embarrassed?
I'm the one who's embarrassed!
You're having dirty thoughts.
I am not!
You two are hitting it off.
You going somewhere?
Hunting the sand golem.
I already took it down.
My reward...!
Calm down, Myne! You can have half!
Mr. Corpse? Your 100 gold coin reward
for defeating the sand golem.
Thanks.
What's with the mask? Lame.
I fought as Corpse, so I have to
collect the reward as him.
Sir Rudolph?
You're Corpse, the one
who defeated the Sand Golem?
You serve me now.
What is this?
You have no right to refuse.
When a holy knight makes a decision,
others must simply obey.
That won't do. He was mine first.
And who are you?
A fresh little girl like you is better off
at home sucking on your mother's—
What are you doing?!
I am not a child.
Well, this is definitely gonna be a problem.
We need to get out of town
while we have the chance!
Wait up!
We need a ride!
The Twilight Swordsman
"The Twilight Swordsman."